Come, come!
Please!
Aziz. Aziz.
Aziz, light!
Aziz, light.
Good.
We start again.
"When the three planets are in eclipse,
the black hole, like a door, is open.
Evil comes...
...spreading terror and chaos."
See the snake, Billy? The ultimate evil.
- Make sure you get the snake.
- Yes, I've got your snakes.
I got all the snakes.
When is the snake act
supposed to occur?
Well, if this is the five...
...and this is the one...
Every 5000 years.
So I've got some time, then.
You bring them water.
Good boy. I will take it to them.
Go with God. Be safe from evil.
You see here these different peoples,
or symbols of people...
...gathering together the four elements
of life: Water, fire, earth, air...
...around a fifth one.
A fifth...
...element.
Forgive me, lord.
They already know too much.
Father.
How are you today?
- Well. You have some glasses?
- Of course.
Father, I'm so glad to see you.
It's the most extraordinary thing.
It's the greatest find in history.
You must be parched.
Oh, yes, yes. I'm sorry.
It's like a battle plan.
Here, the good. Here, the evil.
And here, a weapon against evil.
I'm going to be famous.
Then let us toast to your fame.
To fame.
Salute.
You can't drink a toast with water.
Billy, in my sack, the grappa.
This I don't understand.
This could be something...
...prehistoric.
I don't know.
But wait.
Here.
Look, look.
They're here.
This man...
...this perfect being.
I know this is the key. I know it.
This divine light they talk about.
What is divine light?
Aziz, light!
Much better. Thank you.
My lord.
Father, this is the most
unbelievable thing I have ever seen.
Don't you think?
Are you German?
Lord, I know he was about
to discover everything.
But there is no worry.
I was there in time.
Priest, you and those before you...
...have served us well.
But war is coming.
Stones not safe on Earth anymore.
This...
...is really amazing.
The fifth element.
Take the stones.
My lord...
...if you take the weapon,
we'll be defenceless when evil returns.
In 300 years, when evil returns...
...so shall we.
Oh, professor.
Professor.
Don't move!
I have a gun!
Please, understand.
They're our friends.
Friends?
Father, they've killed the professor!
They're monsters!
I'll explain everything.
- You're with them?
- Look at me.
I am your friend.
- No, Father.
- Billy, look at me!
Please, put the gun down.
Billy, no!
Hurry! The wall is closing!
Here is your mission:
Pass your knowledge to the next priest
as it was passed on to you.
I will do as you command, but please,
hurry, you still have time.
Time not important.
Only life important.
I will fulfil my mission!
You can count on me!
I will pass the knowledge
until your return.
- Anything yet?
- No, sir.
- Not even a temperature?
- The analysers have jammed.
One shows a million degrees,
the others minus 5000.
Let's see it.
It's taking shape.
Send out a probe.
Ladies and gentlemen, the president
of the Federated Territories.
On air with General Staedert
in 30 seconds.
I saved this seat for you, Father.
President on the line.
We're in position.
I have to address the Supreme Council.
Just the facts.
There are no results from the chemical
and molecular analysis yet.
All the calibres are overshot.
We're initiating
thermonucleatic imaging.
What you're saying is,
you don't know what this is.
All we know is,
it just keeps getting bigger.
Recommendation?
My philosophy is shoot first
and ask questions later.
I don't like uninvited guests.
- All right, then, Staedert...
- Mr. President?
Priest Vito Cornelius,
expert of astrophenomenon.
I have a different theory
to offer you, sir.
You have 20 seconds.
Imagine that this...
...thing is not anything
that can be identified...
...because it prefers not to be.
Wherever there is life,
it brings death...
...because it is evil. Absolute evil.
- One more reason to shoot first.
Evil begets evil, Mr. President.
Shooting will only make it stronger.
Probe will obtain objective
in five seconds.
Growth rate is at 27%.
Your theory is interesting,
but we don't have time.
Time is of no importance.
Only life is important.
You're right.
That's exactly what we'll do.
We'll protect the life of 200 billion
of my fellow citizens.
You may fire when ready.
Up-front loading of a 1 20- ZR missile.
Marker lights on the objective.
Its structure solidified on the surface.
I think it's anticipating the attack.
That denotes intelligence.
The most terrible intelligence
imaginable, Mr. President.
1 20's loaded.
The ship is in combat formation.
Missiles are loaded.
- Staedert.
- Yes, sir.
- I have a doubt.
- I don't, Mr. President.
What happened?
Can you hear me?
Staedert, what happened?
- Did you destroy it?
- I'm about to, sir.
The planet has increased
diameter by 200%.
It's moving towards the ship.
What do we have
that's bigger than 240?
Nothing, sir.
Staedert, do you hear me?
Get out of there.
I don't want an incident.
Do you hear me?
Get out of there.
Can you hear me, Staedert?
Do you understand? Listen.
This is the president.
That's an order.
Do you understand me?
Do you hear me?
Get out of there!
Good God!
Four a day.
I'm trying.
To quit is my goal.
I'm up.
All right, I'm up.
God.
Hey, dog brain, Finger here.
- Hi, sweetie.
- I love you too.
You haven't called me that
since basic training.
- I was talking to the cat.
- Oh, yeah, I forgot...
... you prefer your cat to the real thing.
At least the cat comes back.
Still pining for that two-timing slut?
There's millions out there.
I don't want a million women.
I just want one.
The perfect one.
- It don't exist, major.
- Yeah, I know.
- What?
- I just found a picture of you.
- How do I look?
- Like shit.
Must be an old picture.
Bring me your hack
for a six-month overhaul.
- Negative.
- ASAP.
I don't need one.
Who sat next to you for 1000 missions?
I know how you drive.
Finger, I drive a cab now,
not a space fighter.
Okay, so tell me. How many points
you got left on your license?
Major, how many points?
At least 50.
Know what?
You gotta learn to lie better.
See you tonight.
Welcome to paradise.
Welcome to Fhloston Paradise.
It's Ruby Rhod,
and I'll tell you live at 5...
... the winner of the super- green
Gemini Croquette Contest!
The winner will go with me
for two days to Fhloston Paradise.
So tune in to Radio Cosmos.
Don't watch all day.
It'll rot your brain.
For a perfect world.
- Give me the cash.
- Been here long?
Long enough.
Come on, give me the cash.
Is that a Z-140? Alleviated titanium.
Neurocharged assault model.
Good thing for me it's not loaded.
- What do you mean, it's not loaded?
- You have to...
...push that little yellow button
to load it.
Take your time.
Want me to...?
There you go.
Give me the cash!
That's a very dangerous gun.
Maybe you better let me
hang on to this one for you.
You don't mind, do you? You sure?
No. Take it. I don't need it.
That's a very nice hat.
You like it?
God!
Please enter your license.
Yes, just a minute.
Welcome on board, Mr. Dallas.
Good morning. Sleep well? Me too.
- I had a horrible nightmare.
- Propulsion 2-X-4.
You have five points left
on your license.
Yeah, thank you for reminding me.
Have a nice day.
Why not?
You have 48 hours.
That's the time it needs to adapt
to our living conditions.
- And then?
- Then it will be too late.
The goal of this thing is not
to fight over money or power...
...but to exterminate life.
All forms of life.
So you're telling me there's nothing
that can stop this.
There is only one thing.
The Mondoshawan have in their
possession the weapon to defeat evil.
Four elements...
...gathered around a fifth...
...supreme being, the ultimate warrior,
created to protect life.
Together they produce
the Light of Creation.
Able to bring life to the farthest
reaches of the universe.
But if evil stands there...
Then what?
Then light turns to dark.
Life to death...
...forever.
A Mondoshawan spaceship requests
permission to enter our territory.
Give it permission to enter
with our warmest regards.
Thank you.
Permission to enter granted.
Showtime.
We are lost.
Aknot, we are connected to Earth.
Mr. Zorg's office.
It's Aknot.
I'm so glad to hear you, Aknot.
The mission is accomplished.
You'll have what you ask ed for
in a few hours.
Good. I'll meet you at my factory.
The attack was by
two unregistered warships.
Close all borders and
declare a state of general alert.
Try to contact the Mondoshawans.
We owe them an explanation.
Three hundred years
of waiting, for nothing.
Go get some rest.
No.
The Mondoshawan...
I am their contact on Earth.
They will come for me.
This is government business.
I'll keep you informed.
The rescue team has reported
from the crash site.
Any survivors?
Only one.
You call that a survivor?
A few cells still alive.
More than I need.
- Have you identified it?
- The computer went off the charts.
Normal human beings
have 40 DNA memo groups...
...which is enough
for any species to perpetuate.
This has 200,000 memo groups.
- Sounds like a freak of nature.
- Yeah, can't wait to meet him.
You okay? Over here.
Excuse me.
General, I want to show you something.
This is a normal human DNA chain.
You, me, anybody, right?
Watch this.
The compositional elements
of his DNA chain are like ours.
There's simply more of them,
with infinite genetic knowledge.
Almost like this being was engineered.
Is there any danger?
We put it through
the cellular hygiene detector.
The cell is, for lack of a better word...
...perfect.
Okay, go ahead.
Mr. Perfect better be polite.
Otherwise, I turn him into cat food.
Activate it.
Tissue processing.
Ten seconds to ultraviolet protection.
This is the last phase.
The cells are bombarded by atoms
which forces the body to react.
That means growing skin.
Wonderful.
Reconstruction complete.
Remove the shield.
I told you. Perfect.
Thermal bandages.
I'd like to take a few pictures...
...for the archives.
- What's she saying?
- Activate the phonic detector.
Is that thing solid?
- Unbreakable.
- Good.
If you want out...
...you'll have to develop
those communication skills.
General alert.
Perfect.
Ladder on 18.
Two men with me.
The rest in the main ventilation.
This way.
Lady, stay calm.
This is the police.
There's nowhere else to go.
Slowly turn around
and put your hands on the floor.
Do you understand me?
She doesn't.
I think we need a flying unit.
This is the police.
We are processing
your identification.
Put your arms up
and follow our instructions.
She has no file.
She dove off.
You just had an accident.
Yes, I know I just had an accident,
you daffy bastard!
You have one point left
on your license.
Look out!
Left!
I can't believe it. Shit.
Any survivors?
Hi.
Are you okay?
Boom.
Boom. Yeah, I understand "boom."
Bada boom.
Big. Big bada boom.
Big...
...bada big boom.
Big boom.
- Yeah, big bada boom.
- Bada boom.
Big boom. Big bada boom.
You're lucky you're not dead.
This is a police control.
Please k eep your hands
on the wheel.
You have an unauthorized
passenger in your vehicle.
We are going to arrest her.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Sorry, honey.
Looks like this is your ride.
Open the door.
Do what they say.
Sorry.
"Please...
...help."
I only got one point left on my license.
I need that to get back to the garage
and get a six-month overhaul.
You understand?
Can you please
open the passenger door?
Please...
...help.
I can't.
I repeat...
...please open the passenger door.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Why not?
Thank you for your cooperation.
Help.
Finger's gonna kill me.
Emergency! Emergency!
One point has been removed.
Yes, I know!
This is so stupid.
Assist in pursuit of yellow cab.
Unit 47, we're on the way...
...as soon as we finish lunch.
Two golden menus.
I'm too old, too tired and too hungry
to go chasing some hot rod.
Thank you so much.
And I'm definitely too thirsty.
Look out!
We got lucky.
If they don't chase you after a mile,
they don't chase you.
Maybe it's two miles.
Hang on.
Look, lady, I only speak English
and bad English!
Run an ID.
I'm all for conversation, but maybe
you can just shut up for a minute!
- He's got a scan blocker.
- Means he's a car thief. Blast him.
I don't know what you did...
...but they are really pissed off!
Hold on!
We're safe for a while.
You want to play soft?
I'll play soft.
You want to play hard?
Let's play hard.
If I get to the fog, we'll be all right.
If we make the fog.
How do they expect us
to find anything in this shit?
We're just going to wait here until
things quiet down, if you don't mind.
Shit.
You okay?
Priest.
You don't need a priest,
just a doctor.
- Vito Cornelius.
- What?
Priest.
Yes?
I'm looking for a priest.
The weddings are one floor down.
Congratulations.
She's not my bride. She's my fare.
She's looking for Vito Cornelius.
The phone book said he lived here.
Yes, that's me,
but I don't know who she is.
Nobody does.
No file, no ID, nothing.
She's got a tattoo on this arm.
Tattoo?
Fifth...
...element.
Finger's gonna kill me.
- Hey! Wake up!
- Who are you?
I brought the girl, remember?
The redhead.
She just dropped in on me.
Started speaking this bizarre language.
It's not bizarre.
It's the divine language.
The ancient language...
...spoken throughout the universe
before time was time.
- He's a she.
- You noticed that.
Yes.
- It's a miracle.
- Miracle she's not dead.
Not a moment to lose. Wake her up.
But gently, because this woman is
mankind's most precious possession.
She is perfect.
Perfect.
More dignified.
Hey, lady...
...wake up.
You're right, I shouldn't have done that.
I was wrong to kiss you.
He said to wake you gently.
You're right.
Just thought you might
remember me from the cab.
Remember?
"Bada boom"?
"Big bada boom"?
Boom. Big bada boom.
In the cab. Look.
I drive a cab. This is me.
Korben Dallas.
Korben. You understand?
Here. Take it, go ahead.
You can call me
when you learn English.
Just kidding.
What is your name?
You.
Korben.
Leeloo Minai Lekarariba-Laminai-Tchai
Ekbat De Sebat.
Good.
That whole thing's your name?
Do you have...
...a shorter name?
Short.
Korben Dallas.
Leeloo.
Korben, Leeloo.
Leeloo, Korben.
- You're sure she's a supreme being?
- Absolutely sure.
Old friends.
Yeah, you're right.
- Ask her for my gun back.
- What's your name?
Korben Dallas.
Thank you for your help.
You've been kind,
but now the girl needs to rest.
She's been on a long trip.
I know. I was there when she landed.
Wait, wait, Father.
She said something
I didn't understand.
- What does "ekto gamat" mean?
- "Never without my permission."
That's what I thought.
I shouldn't have kissed her.
Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
I forgot your food.
How about some nice Thai food?
Yeah, yeah, hold on.
Buddy, I'm waiting all day here.
- Finger.
- Where is the cab?
- Car's running fine. Purrs like a kitten.
- Fine. What "fine"?
I know you.
"Fine" ain't in your v ocabulary.
You can tell your old buddy Finger
what happened.
What? You save the planet?
You dinged the fender again.
That's it, right?
I was on my way to see you,
and a fare fell in my lap.
One of these big fares
you can't resist.
How big?
Five-nine...
...blue eyes...
...long legs, great skin.
You know. Perfect.
I see.
And this perfect fare, she got a name?
Yeah. Leeloo.
What's she doing?
Learning our history,
the last 5000 years that she missed.
She's been asleep for a while.
I know she's been through a lot,
but we don't have much time.
You're right.
Chicken.
Good.
I'm really sorry to interrupt you...
...but the case...
...with the stones...
...where is it?
Stolen?
Who in God's name
would do such a thing?
Excuse me, sir. The council is worried
about the economy heating up.
Is it possible to fire 500,000?
I thought from a smaller company,
like one of the cab companies.
Fire one million.
But 500,000...
One million. Fine, sir.
Sorry to have disturbed you.
It's for the Supreme...
Sorry.
I didn't know your size,
and I found you this makeup box.
You just put it like that.
Yes, there was a man with a limp...
...came here a month ago
asking about the stones.
Said he was an art dealer.
What was his name?
I'm so bad with names.
- They really make her...
- Perfect, I know.
What did she say?
She says she knows
exactly where they are.
My dear Aknot, how about
those two planes you borrowed?
Aknot, is that you?
What an ugly face.
It doesn't suit you.
Take it off.
That's better.
Never be ashamed of who you are.
You're warriors. Be proud.
So what if the federal government
scattered you to the wind.
What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger.
Your time for revenge is at hand.
The ZF-1.
It's light. The handle's adjustable
for easy carrying.
Breaks down into four parts,
undetectable by X-ray. Discreet.
A word on firepower:
Titanium recharger, 3000-round clip
with bursts of 3 to 300.
With the replay button,
a Zorg invention, it's even easier.
One shot...
...and replay sends every
following shot to the same location.
And to finish the job,
all the Zorg oldies but goldies.
Rocket launcher.
Arrow launcher with exploding
or poisonous gas heads.
Very practical.
Our famous net launcher.
The always-efficient flamethrower.
My favourite.
And for the grand finale,
the all-new ice-cube system.
Four full crates
delivered right on time.
And what about you, my dear Aknot?
Did you bring me what I asked you for?
Yes.
Magnificent.
This...
This case is empty.
- What do you mean, empty?
- Empty...
...the opposite of full.
This case is supposed to be full!
Anyone care to explain?
The Guardians gave the stones
to someone they could trust.
Who took another route.
She's supposed
to contact this person...
...in a hotel.
And she's looking
for the address. Easy.
Dot.
It's Planet Fhloston,
in the Angel Constellation.
- We're saved.
- I'm screwed.
You asked for a case.
We brought you a case.
A case with four stones in it!
Not one or two or three,
but four!
Four stones!
But what the hell am I supposed to do
with an empty case?
We are warriors, not merchants.
But you can still count!
It's easy. Look at my fingers.
Four stones, four crates.
Zero stones, zero crates!
Pack everything up!
We're out of here!
We risked our lives.
I believe a little compensation
is in order.
So you are merchants after all.
Leave him one crate for the cause.
I don't like warriors.
Too narrow-minded, no subtlety...
...and worse, they fight
for hopeless causes, honour.
Honour's killed millions of people.
Hasn't saved a single one.
I'll tell you what I do like:
A killer.
A dyed-in-the-wool killer,
cold-blooded, clean and methodical.
A real killer picking up the ZF-1...
...would've asked about the red button
on the bottom of the gun.
Bring me the priest.
I got everything we need
to know about Fhloston Paradise...
...and a blueprint of the hotel.
Good work, my son.
Now to find a way there.
It won't be easy.
There's a charity ball tomorrow.
Flights are full,
and the hotel will be guarded.
But there must be a way.
I'll get it.
Weddings?
Not really.
- Mr. Zorg would like to talk to you.
- Mister who?
Mr. Zorg.
Jean-Baptiste Emmanuel...
...Zorg.
It's nice to see you again, Father.
I remember you now.
The so-called art dealer.
I'm glad you got your memory back,
because you're gonna need it.
Where are the stones?
I don't know. Even if I did,
I wouldn't tell someone like you.
Why?
- What's wrong with me?
- I try to serve life.
But you only...
...seem to want to destroy it.
Father...
...you're so wrong. Let me explain.
Life, which you so nobly serve...
...comes from destruction, disorder
and chaos.
Now, take this empty glass.
Peaceful, serene, boring.
But if it is...
...destroyed...
Look at all these little things.
So busy now.
Notice how each one is useful.
What a lovely ballet ensues,
so full of form and colour.
Now, think of all those people
that created them.
Technicians, engineers. People who
can feed their children tonight...
...so those children can grow up
and have children of their own...
...and so on and so forth.
Thus adding to the great chain...
...of life.
Water. Fruit.
You see, Father, by creating
a little destruction...
A cherry.
...l'm, in fact, encouraging life.
In reality, you and I
are in the same business.
Cheers.
Where's the robot
to pat you on the back?
Or the engineer?
Or their children, maybe?
There, you see how all your
so-called power counts for nothing?
How your entire empire
of destruction comes crashing down...
...all because of one, little cherry.
You saved my life...
...and in return, I'll spare yours...
...for now.
You're a monster, Zorg.
I know.
Torture who you have to,
the president, I don't care.
Just bring me those stones.
You have one hour.
It's gobbling up
all the satellites in the galaxy.
Why in the hell
is it eating up all the satellites?
We're working on it, Mr. President.
The Mondoshawan deplore the incident
but accept our apologies.
And the stones? Did you find them?
- They weren't on board.
- What?
The Mondoshawan never
fully trusted the human race.
They gave them
to someone they do trust.
Her name is Plavalaguna.
She's a diva.
She's singing at a charity ball
in Fhloston Paradise.
She has the stones with her.
The Mondoshawans will help.
All we have to do is send someone
to get the stones.
Excellent.
I want this operation to be
discreet as possible.
No troops. No big operation.
I want your best man
to go undercover.
I have the perfect one.
You got a message.
Not gonna open it?
Could be important.
Like the last two were important.
First one was from my wife
telling me she's leaving.
The second was from my lawyer
telling me he was leaving with my wife.
That is bad luck.
But grandfather say:
"It never rain every day."
This is good news, guaranteed.
I bet you lunch.
Okay.
Come on.
"You are fired."
Oh, I'm sorry.
At least I won lunch.
Good philosophy.
See good in bad. I like.
- Hello.
- Korben, sweetheart.
You got brok en fingers?
You can't punch my number?
- Hi, Mom.
- Seventeen messages.
Don't say your machine is
brok en again. They last 1000 years.
Mr. Kim, you should go.
This'll take a minute.
You don't feed your cat a croquette,
who you love more than me.
- She didn't breast-feed you. I did.
- Goodbye, Mr. Dallas.
Good fortune for you.
You don't have a girl.
I'll never be a grandmother.
- It bring you good luck!
- Yeah, sure.
What are you talking about?
No, all I want is an explanation.
I just got in.
I just smashed my cab.
I lost my job. I got mugged.
Besides that, everything's peachy.
Thanks for asking.
Now, settle down
and explain this to me.
If I'd won a trip, I'd know.
I would've been notified.
I'll call you back.
General, how nice to see you
in the 5000 block.
Nice apartment, major.
You've settled into a wonderful life.
Heard you lost your job.
You heard that?
Don't worry. I'll get another job.
Don't bother. We have one for you.
"Major Dallas, you've been
selected for a mission."
- What mission?
- To save the world.
"You leave for Fhloston Paradise.
Get four stones from the diva
Plavalaguna and bring them back."
- Any questions?
- Yeah, just one. Why me?
- I retired six months ago, remember?
- Three reasons.
One, as a member of the Elite
Special Forces Unit of the army...
...you are an expert in the use of
all necessary weapons and spacecraft.
Two, you're the most highly
decorated member of your unit.
- The third?
- Of all the members of your unit...
...you're the only one left alive.
- Check your messages?
- I've had enough good news.
Might be important.
You're a winner!
You've won the Gemini Contest
and a trip to Fhloston Paradise for two.
Here are your tickets.
You rigged the contest?
Congratulations.
You couldn't be more discreet?
Old tricks are the best tricks.
Major Iceborg will
accompany you as your wife.
I am not going.
Why not?
Excuse me, general.
Who is it? Who is it?
- My wife.
- You remarried?
Yes. No. I just met this girl,
but I'm gonna marry her.
I love her,
but she hates the military.
She knows the military
ruined my last marriage.
She can't have anything to do with it.
If she sees you, she'll kill me.
- Major...
- You gotta hide somewhere.
- You've gotta help me.
- We'd love to, but where can we hide?
- We don't have time for this.
- It's just for one minute.
You have no idea
how much you're helping me.
No idea... You have no idea.
- I'm going to be happily married.
- Major! Major!
- The three of us won't fit.
- Sure you will.
Major!
You're on my foot.
Major! Major!
I'm really sorry to resort to this,
Mr. Wallace...
Dallas.
We heard about your good luck
and need your tickets for Fhloston.
Is this the way priests vacation?
- Not vacation. We're on a mission.
- What kind?
We have to save the world, my son.
- You're gonna save the world?
- Yes!
Down there. Down there.
This is a police control.
This is not an exercise.
Come on, get in.
For one minute, all right?
Just stay here for one minute.
- This is a police control.
- Don't touch anything.
This is not an exercise.
Can you please spread your legs...
... and place your hands
in the yellow circles.
- What are you doing?
- Saving you so you can save the world.
Yeah, but l...
I think this is the door.
No name, no number.
Let's see it.
Are you classified as human?
Negative. I am a meat Popsicle.
I found him.
Mr. Korben Dallas?
Sir, can you put your hands
in the yellow circles, please?
Smoke you!
Wrong answer.
The police control
is now terminated.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Have a nice day.
We got the guy.
Wasn't easy, but we bagged him.
- Thanks for the tip.
- Glad to be of help, my friend.
The guy's been arrested
for uranium smuggling.
All I have to do now is go
to the airport, take his place...
...and I'll be in Fhloston in four hours.
Don't come back without the stones.
Korben Dallas. We got him.
Perfect.
Akanit, take command.
Go to Fhloston and get the stones.
If Zorg really wants them...
...he'll have to negotiate.
Revenge is at hand.
Oh, I am so sorry.
I forgot about the autowash.
There's an autowash
in that shower.
I'm so sorry.
Autowash.
Autowash, yes.
Autowash, in the shower.
It's funny. I've met you twice today.
Both times,
you've ended up in my arms.
It's my lucky day.
Lucky day.
Did you hear something?
Cornelius.
Autowash.
- I'm so sorry.
- I don't need your help.
- Want a cup of coffee?
- Yes, please.
Autowash.
Coffee's not really my specialty.
But you must drink a lot
of coffee, being a priest.
I know. I'm not proud of what I did.
I had no choice.
I'll take the mission.
- Did you get them?
- Yeah.
Good.
- "Leeloo Dallas."
- "Multi-pass."
"Korben David Dallas." Perfect.
I can't be your husband. I'm too old.
Now, David is...
...in great shape. He'll protect you.
Now, please, go to the diva, collect
the stones and meet me at the temple.
Now. Yes.
Okay.
Last call for Fhloston Paradise.
Hurry up.
The tickets.
- ID, please.
- I'm sorry.
- There.
- In here?
Mr. Dallas?
Yeah.
Congratulations
on winning the contest.
Oh, right. Okay.
- Sorry for the mess.
- The mess?
The garbage.
Made it!
I was so afraid I wouldn't make it...
...so I sent David
to pick up my boarding pass.
Now David has to go.
Thank you. Bye.
I am Korben Dallas.
Please report infractions
immediately to the spaceport.
And this is?
Leeloo Dallas. Multi-pass.
Multi-pass.
She knows it's a multi-pass.
My wife. We're newlyweds. Just met.
Bump into each other,
sparks happen... She knows.
Anyway, we're in love.
I mean, I know
she's made to be strong.
She's also so fragile, so human.
You know what I mean?
- You want some more?
- Yeah.
Make that two.
- Where's Leeloo?
- On the plane with Mr. Dallas.
- What?!
- I'm sorry. I didn't know what to do.
But this is not possible.
This is not possible.
You want some more?
This is all my fault.
It is my mission.
I shouldn't have given it to you.
I know.
- The key to the temple.
- Oh, no.
Prepare for our arrival.
I go to face my destiny.
I don't want to go to Egypt.
Dallas? Korben Dallas?
That's me.
Just a minute, please.
It will take just one more minute.
We'll be right back.
Mr. Dallas, we really need you now.
Ruby Rhod is broadcasting live
and he needs you for an interview.
Miss?
Multi-pass.
Tell Aknot that plan A flopped.
Go to plan B.
Aliens ahead. Spread out.
Backup unit, zone 18.
Ruby Rhod is the biggest radio star.
It's an honour to be on his talk show.
He's so green.
I'm sure you're excited.
I'm on vacation
and don't want to be bothered.
I prefer to remain anonymous.
Korben Dallas!
Here he is! The winner of
the Gemini Croquette Contest.
This boy is fuelled like fire,
so start melting, ladies...
...because he is hotter than hot.
He's hot, hot, hot!
The right size, the right build,
the right hair, the right on.
Right on.
And he's got something to say...
...to those 50 billion pairs
of ears out there.
Pop it, D-man.
Hi.
Unbelievable.
Quiver, ladies.
He's gonna set the world on fire.
Right here from 5 to 7.
You'll know everything
there is to know about the D-man.
His dreams...
...his desires...
...his most intimate of intimates.
And from what I'm looking at,
intimate is his middle name.
So tell me, my man...
...you nervous in the service?
Not really.
Freeze those knees because Korben's
in the place and he's on the case.
Yesterday's frog
will be tomorrow's prince...
...of Fhloston Paradise!
The hotel of a thousand and one
follies and lollies.
A magic fountain flowing
with non-stop wine, women and...
...hootchie-kootchie-koo...
...all night long.
Start licking stamps, girls, because
he'll have you writing home to Mama.
Here, from 5 to 7,
I'll be your voice, your tongue...
...on the trail of the sexiest man
of the year: D-man, your man...
...my man.
End of transmission.
Okay, Ruby.
See you tomorrow at 5.
How was it?
It was just absolutely green.
Green like what?
Crystal green.
Any kind of green you want...
...tree green, emerald, pond green.
Korben, sweetheart, what was that?
It was bad! It had nothing!
No fire! No energy!
I have a show to run here.
It must pop, pop, pop!
So tomorrow, from 5 to 7...
...please act like you have
more than a two-word vocabulary.
It must be green! Okay? Okay?
Can I talk to you for a second?
Just talk to you?
I didn't come here to play
Pumba on the radio.
Tomorrow, from 5 to 7,
you'll give yourself a hand.
- Green?
- Super-green.
Dallas? Korben Dallas?
That's me.
I only have one Korben Dallas
on my list, and he's checked in.
That's impossible. I am Korben Dallas.
Sorry, sir. Boarding is finished.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
I need to talk to someone!
I don't believe this!
This is not an exercise.
This is a police control.
I'm sorry. I'm calm.
There's been a mistake.
To make your flight short...
...flight attendants are switching
on the sleep regulator...
...which will regulate your sleeping
during the flight.
Thank you.
Hi.
- You speak English now.
- Yes. I learn.
Good.
Leeloo, we are not on vacation.
I'm on an important mission.
I work for some important people.
If I hadn't come to get you,
you'd be in trouble.
- Understand? Big trouble?
- Yes.
But you, no trouble.
Me, fifth element.
Supreme being.
Me protect you.
Sleep.
- Sweet dreams, Mr. Dallas.
- No, wait...
Sleep regulator operative
in zone one.
Thank you.
Zone two, are you operative?
Zone two?
Everything's ready, captain.
- Mr. Rhod.
- What?
Assume your individual position.
But I want all positions!
Mr. Rhod!
- Parasites in landing gear.
- Ground, you copy?
Got it. Front gear.
Hey, man, give me some heat, man!
We need some heat here, man!
Get some heat!
Some heat over here, man!
Good shit, man.
Put the heat over here, man!
Thank you!
Thank you very much!
Come, come.
Give me this. Give me this.
Take that.
Mr. Rhod!
You can call me Ruby.
Fuelled and ready to go.
I'll buy you one.
Have you taken off already?
- I'm not on the plane.
- What?
The real Dallas took my place.
I don't understand.
Are you making fun of me?
No, no, no! I swear! I swear!
I never felt this way before
with a human.
- Really?
- Yeah!
I've tried everything, believe me.
There's no way to get on the plane.
- Ground is clear.
- Roger. Ready for liftoff?
Confirmed.
Not there. No, please, not there.
Please, not there.
- Power pressure?
- Primed.
- Protection?
- Confirmed.
Power increase.
Ten seconds.
I am...
...a little...
...disappointed.
- Five...
- lf there is one thing I do not like...
- Three...
...it is to be...
...two...
...disappointed.
...one...
- Sorry, this will never happen again.
- I know.
...liftoff.
- Landing gear secure.
- Roger. Checklist for light speed.
Sir, we're finally getting something.
It's sending radio wavelengths.
- What does it want with radio waves?
- Maybe it wants to make a call.
Zorg's office.
I told you I did not
want to be disturbed.
You don't want to be disturbed
except if it's Mr. Shadow...
...and it's Mr. Shadow on the line.
It's Shadow again.
Zorg here.
- Am I disturbing you?
- No, no, I was just...
Where are you?
Not far now.
Good.
Good, good.
How are the stones?
Fine. Fine. Just fine.
I'll have the...
I'll have the four stones
you asked for any time now...
...but it wasn't easy.
My costs have tripled.
Money is of no importance.
I want the stones.
The stones...
...will be here.
I'll see to it personally.
I will be among you...
... soon.
- We lost it.
- We lost the signal.
Damn!
We've begun our descent
toward Fhloston Paradise.
The local time is 3:20 p.m.
Auto-temperature is currently
85 degrees Fahrenheit.
We hope you enjoyed your flight
and hope to see you again soon.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to paradise.
Excuse me, dear. Excuse me.
Excuse me, please.
Parasites in the main ventilation.
Again? I'll get it.
Have we arrived yet?
- Yeah.
- Oh, good.
We have twelve swimming pools
and two on the rooftop.
All the restaurants are between
level two and level 10.
The planet Fhloston has 400 beaches,
all accessible until 5 p.m.
Then the airship goes higher
to offer you a better view.
- Is the diva here yet?
- Not yet.
- Any tickets left for the opera?
- You have a seat reserved, front row...
...next to Ruby Rhod!
He's so talented, don't you think?
I love him. He's so sexy.
He has your ticket,
and he'll be here in 20 minutes.
Where can I get something to wear?
- Enjoy your evening, Mr. Dallas.
- Thank you.
You miserable bastard,
I never should've pushed you out.
I was in labour for days,
and this is how you repay me?
- I should've gotten a robot.
- Come on, Ma.
I should be there, not you.
I need a tan. I need a cocktail.
Get the case in.
Hello, Ms. Diva. I'm Fog.
Welcome to the... I'm security.
Welcome to the... Tall...
- Can I talk to you?
- Sure. Yeah.
- What's your name?
- Fog.
Ms. Plavalaguna is glad
that you're here.
She'll give you what you've come
to get after the concert.
Stay here.
You're listening to Radio Cosmos
and it is now 5 p.m.
- Helm to 108.
- Yes, sir.
Helm 108!
Helm to 108.
Time to join Ruby Rhod
and Korben Dallas...
... the lucky winner
of the Gemini Croquette Contest.
Coming at you live from Fhloston...
Paradise!
Ruby Rhod at your service with Korben
and the manager of this hotel...
...and Miss Gemini Croquette
in person...
...and 8000 other lucksters here...
...to enjoy the privilege of the
unique concert of Miss Plavalaguna!
Now we enter what must be...
...the most beautiful concert hall
of all the universe!
A perfect replica
of the old opera house...
...but who cares?
To my right, a row of ministers,
more sinisters than ministers.
To my left, Baby Ray,
star of stage and screen.
He's not gonna get much
out of this concert. He's stone-deaf!
To who?
And here we have Roy Von Baker,
king of laser ball.
The Emperor of Kodar Japhet
and his lovely daughter.
"I love to sing,"
she recently confessed to me.
By the way, I have a recording
of her talented voice.
I play the rest after the concert.
Now it's time...
...for Korben
to say the word of the day.
Tell me, my man, you happy
here in the big world?
Thrilled.
And now champagne!
Commercial!
Break for 30 seconds.
Showtime.
I have a ship in trouble
requesting permission to dock.
Put him in the docking garage.
Inform security.
- Permission granted for one hour.
- More than I need.
- Yes?
- Champagne for the diva.
I'll take it.
I found it.
Get her!
It was an ambush.
If it's war they want,
it's war they'll get!
Bravo! Bravo!
My compliments, little lady.
Thank you for doing all the dirty work.
I couldn't have done a better job myself.
Hand over the stones.
Nobody move!
I'm taking over the ship!
Hands up!
Ruby! Ruby!
I know this music.
Let's change the beat.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I think we're being attacked.
I don't know who they are,
but they're everywhere.
I see one. They're warriors,
and they're ugly.
They got big teeth, big foreheads,
and they stink.
Mangalores.
The government sent me to help you.
Stay calm.
If somebody hears this,
come and get me. I'm in the first row.
- You must give her the stones.
- Who?
The fifth element.
The supreme being sent to Earth
to save the universe.
- Leeloo?
- Yes.
But she's more fragile than she seems.
She needs your help...
...and your love...
...or she will die.
- Stay with me.
- Help!
If you want something done,
do it yourself.
Come on, honey. You can't die.
Listen to me. Wake up!
- Where are the stones?
- What?
The stones. Where are the stones?
The stones.
They're not here.
The stones, where are they?
In me.
What?
Oh, my God, Korben.
Korben, another one coming.
- I think we should go.
- One minute. One minute.
Hey, you!
I said you.
- I'm not with him.
- Where's the other?
I said one minute.
Ruby, hold this gun.
What do you want me to do?
Come on. Put your hand on it.
- What do I do?
- Lf he moves, squeeze the trigger.
- I don't feel right. I don't feel right.
- The stones are "in me."
I got a headache. This ain't me.
Sorry.
Think he'll be okay?
Oh, my God, Korben.
Another one coming.
Shit. Three coming.
You guard this with your life,
or you'll look like him. You green?
- Green.
- Super- green?
Is that your idea
of a discreet operation?
Don't worry. I know my man.
He'll calm things down.
Move! Move!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is amazing.
Let me do it.
Oh, my God. Korben Dallas,
my man, is in trouble.
The gun!
The gun! Give me the gun.
I'm gonna go and try to see
if I can see something a little closer.
Yes, the gun. Yeah.
Thanks, Ray.
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
I'm not armed!
Get up!
You've got the wrong guy! Don't shoot!
I'm not armed!
Oh, my God.
I'm on vacation.
Don't shoot me, please.
I'm on a vacation. I won a...
...contest.
Gemini Croquette's to
Fhloston Paradise.
Down.
- Wait a minute.
- Get down!
- He's trying to say something to me.
- Down!
Sorry, my man.
Where are you?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
They're coming. They're coming.
Don't move.
- What you doing?
- Count to 10.
- Was that a bomb?
- Shut up and count!
One, two, three, four, five...
...six, seven, eight...
...nine...
Ten.
I am very disappointed!
Korben, what are you looking for?
Control room.
- This is it.
- I'll be over here.
Let's go!
Quiet! Quiet!
You in charge?
How many are out there?
- I don't know.
- Let's count.
Seven on the left. Five on the right.
Four on the right. Two on the left.
Find the leader.
They won't fight without the leader.
One more shot and we start
killing hostages.
- That's the leader.
- Send someone to negotiate.
I've never negotiated.
You mind if I try?
No, no. Sure, sure.
We're sending somebody in
to negotiate!
Anybody else want to negotiate?
Where did he learn
to negotiate like that?
I wonder.
Where's Ruby?
I thought he was dead.
Master!
It was nothing, really.
Just a helping hand.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is Ruby Rhod...
...still alive.
What's wrong with you? It hurt!
I realize that you must be
pretty mad at me...
...but I'm fighting for a noble cause.
Yes, you're trying to save the world.
I remember.
- Right now, I'm trying to save Leeloo.
- Leeloo's in trouble?
When is Leeloo not in trouble?
- There. Where's that?
- The diva's suite.
Hang on.
Here, come on. How do you
get yourself into these positions?
Come on.
I'm here. It's all right.
Everything's okay now.
Listen.
I got the stones.
Just take it easy, all right?
My man, my man, what's this thing
with all these numbers?
It's... It's...
If it was a bomb...
...the alarms would go off because
all these hotels have bomb detectors.
This is a Type A alert.
For security reasons,
the hotel must be evacuated.
Proceed calmly to the lifeboats...
Stay calm!
... located in the main hallways.
Please, stay calm!
Korben, my man,
you know how to stop this, right?
Two minutes to complete evacuation.
- Get back!
- Evacuation! Evacuation!
Sorry, you can't stay here.
There's a bomb in the hotel.
I know.
- I don't want to die.
- Please, my son.
Get in.
One minute to total evacuation.
This one.
Forty-five seconds.
Get her strapped in.
Korben, my man,
you know how to fly this thing?
Just like driving a cab.
How we gonna get out the door?
Fifteen seconds.
Ten, nine, eight...
... seven, six, five...
For the honour.
Oh, no.
You should hold on.
Like driving a cab.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is now 7 p.m. Time for the news.
See you tomorrow
for a new adventure.
End of transmission.
That's the best show I ever did.
Major Dallas has
the five elements on board...
...and the priest is guiding them
to the temple.
We're saved.
The diva said
I should take care of you.
Humans act so strange.
What do you mean?
Everything you created...
...is used to destroy.
We call it human nature.
You learn that on your screen?
I'm not finished yet. I'm up to V.
V is good.
Some very good words in V.
Like what?
Valiant.
Vulnerable.
Very beautiful.
Oh, of course, Munro!
- Mr. President?
- Yes, now what?
We have a problem.
It's advancing?
It's not only advancing,
it's moving at incredible speed.
And do you have any idea
where it's heading?
Korben, there's a general on the phone.
I'll give you the president.
Major Dallas, I first would like
to salute a warrior.
You're a shining example of this army.
In the name of the Federation...
Any idea when you'll get to the point?
Okay. There's a ball of fire 1 200 miles
in diameter heading straight for Earth...
... and we have no idea how to stop it.
That's the problem.
How much time do we have?
If its speed remains constant,
in an hour and 57 minutes.
I'll call you back in two hours.
Hello?
They just landed in the desert.
Good job, David.
- Put her in the centre.
- Where? Here?
You got it figured out, Father?
This one should be fire.
- You know how this works?
- Theoretically.
The four stones should go around.
The fifth element should be
in the middle...
...and then the weapon
against evil should work.
- You've never seen this work?
- No.
Every weapon has a manual.
I'm sure this has one too.
- That's it. That's it.
- Match up the symbols. Go! Go!
Wind.
My man, what you doing?
- What?
- What you doing?
Trying to keep you in the DJ business.
Fire.
Done.
- So, what happens now?
- So now, we have to open them.
- And you know how to do that, right?
- Theoretically...
...no.
Leeloo, honey, wake up.
You have to help us.
How do you open these stones?
Wind blows.
Fire burns.
Yes, I know all that.
But how do you open these stones?
Rain...
...falls.
What does it mean?
I think that...
Maybe it's a charade.
A game or something.
If we don't get these stones open
in five minutes, we're dead.
- Dead?
- Yes, dead.
Too late.
- We've lost contact with them.
- Three minutes.
I think mine is broken.
Why I gotta get the broke one?
We're never gonna make it.
Korben. Korben, it moved!
- Show me what you did.
- Nothing.
Shut up, shut up!
Calm down. Show me
what you did, step by step.
- I was just standing here.
- Quickly.
I put my hands on the top
like this, and I said:
"We're not gonna make it."
And that's it?
Korben, my man.
Wind.
She said, "Wind blows."
Everyone take a stone.
Water for water. Fire for fire.
Earth for Earth. Go!
Earth.
Open the other one.
Korben, my man, I have no fire.
I have no matches. Do you have any?
I stopped smoking. Father, you smoke?
Got some matches? We need some fire.
We gonna die.
Don't breathe.
Fire.
One minute.
Let's go, Leeloo.
Wake up. Wake up.
It's time for you to work now.
Protect life...
...until death.
Listen to me! Listen to me.
Listen, I know you're very tired.
I'll take you on vacation.
A real vacation, just you and me.
But if you don't do something
right now, we'll all die.
What's the use of saving life
when you see what you do with it?
Lt'll be entering the atmosphere
in 40 seconds.
Leeloo, you're right. You're right.
But there are some things...
...very nice things worth saving,
beautiful things.
Beautiful things.
Like love?
Yes, love. That's good. That's good.
That's a good example.
Love is worth saving.
I don't know love.
I was built to protect, not to love.
So there's no use
for me other than this.
You're wrong.
You're wrong. You're wrong.
I need you. I need you, very much.
Why?
Because...
Tell her, Korben.
Tell me. Please.
Why do you need me?
- Because...
- Tell me.
- Because l...
Because I love you.
I love you.
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
...six, five, four, three...
...two, one...
Scanner imaging has confirmed
the dark planet dead.
The planet seems to have stopped
at 62 miles from impact.
What's wrong with you?
What you screaming for?
Every five minutes,
it's a bomb or something.
I'm leaving.
Mr. President.
Let me introduce Professor Mactilburgh
who runs the centre.
It's an honour, Mr. President.
Where are my two heroes?
They were so tired from their ordeal,
we put them in the reactor.
I have 19 meetings after this.
Let me see if they're revived.
Thank you.
We go live in one minute,
Mr. President.
They're...
...not ready.
They need...
...five more minutes.
- You have 20 seconds.
- No, ma'am, I tried. No, ma'am.
- Who's that?
Some woman.
Claims to be Korben's mother.
Give it here.
Mrs. Dallas, this is the president.
On behalf of the Federation...
That doesn't even sound lik e him.
The president's an idiot.
You don't sound lik e an idiot.
If you don't want to talk to your mother,
just av oid me as usual.
I'll throw myself in traffic.
I'll Saran Wrap myself to the bed.
Subtitles by: "K3LtZ" using SUBRIP